[music]
Guess who's adulting? I finally decided
to meet with a financial advisor. Yes,
mama.
What if
I say no?
Girl,
stop overthinking.
For all you know, you'll benefit more
from this. You know what? Actually,
Hi there, I'm Jay and I'm here to help
you have a better understanding of your
financial goals. Don't worry, the last
thing I will do is judge your journey.
If you can't decide yet, no commitment.
Basically, we'll talk about your needs
and goals,
what you can do to be financially
prepared, and how a trusted partner can
help. It's all about sharing with you
clear, practical [music] financial
advice
goals. We will take it [music] step by
step overwhelm.
Oh, that sounds nice.
All right, I think [music] I'm now
excited to meet him.
>> Oh, good decision, my adult friend.
Talk to a Sunlife advisor today.